<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-12-04T15:51:41+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Dev Talk Show</title><subtitle>Developers talking to developers about developing. This is the parking lot conversation we would  typically have after going to a user group meeting and just talking. At the end of those sessions  we would typically say, 'we should have recorded this.' So here you go!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Developer Resolutions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/12/01/Developer-Resolutions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Developer Resolutions" /><published>2021-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/video/2021/12/01/Developer-Resolutions</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/12/01/Developer-Resolutions.html">&lt;p&gt;TheDevTalkShow is going to chat about what’s coming in 2022 for each of us and maybe write a little code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Xqu7xTvTB1o&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Rich Ross</name></author><category term="video" /><summary type="html">TheDevTalkShow is going to chat about what’s coming in 2022 for each of us and maybe write a little code.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Exploring .NET 6 LIVE - Post .NET Conf Wrap Up</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/11/17/Exploring-.NET-6.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exploring .NET 6 LIVE - Post .NET Conf Wrap Up" /><published>2021-11-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-11-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/video/2021/11/17/Exploring-.NET-6</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/11/17/Exploring-.NET-6.html">&lt;p&gt;.NET 6 was released at .NET Conf 2021 and we’re going to talk about new features, try it out live, and maybe explore some new features in IDEs that go with it.  There’s been a lot going on in this space and after .NET Conf we’ll have plenty of thoughts about it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We’d also love to know what you think and can’t wait to hear your ideas for what we should try.  We love to explore things live and learn together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; .NET Conf 2021 is November 9-11: https://www.dotnetconf.net/.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wwOFy4aZSpw&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Rich Ross</name></author><category term="video" /><summary type="html">.NET 6 was released at .NET Conf 2021 and we’re going to talk about new features, try it out live, and maybe explore some new features in IDEs that go with it. There’s been a lot going on in this space and after .NET Conf we’ll have plenty of thoughts about it. We’d also love to know what you think and can’t wait to hear your ideas for what we should try. We love to explore things live and learn together. .NET Conf 2021 is November 9-11: https://www.dotnetconf.net/.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Live Coding - Automated Content Creation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/11/10/Automated-Content-Creation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Live Coding - Automated Content Creation" /><published>2021-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/video/2021/11/10/Automated-Content-Creation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/11/10/Automated-Content-Creation.html">&lt;p&gt;In an ongoing collection of ideas of how we can automate some of the routine tasks we need to do as a weekly live stream, we want to create a blog post as a follow-up to each show here on The Dev Talk Show.  the blog post contains the title, description, and link to the video on our YouTube archive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a number of different ways to do this and our current plan focuses on GitHub actions to do the heavy lifting.  Our data for the post is stored with the YouTube video so we will need to reach out to that service.  The custom GitHub Action will then pull this all together in a file and check this into the GitHub pages repo, which is where we host our blog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a Live Coding session, so join us on Wed at 8:30 and see if we can pull this off or watch it go back into the backlog.  Either way, this will be fun to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xLPyxKDmL00&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Rich Ross</name></author><category term="video" /><summary type="html">In an ongoing collection of ideas of how we can automate some of the routine tasks we need to do as a weekly live stream, we want to create a blog post as a follow-up to each show here on The Dev Talk Show. the blog post contains the title, description, and link to the video on our YouTube archive.There are a number of different ways to do this and our current plan focuses on GitHub actions to do the heavy lifting. Our data for the post is stored with the YouTube video so we will need to reach out to that service. The custom GitHub Action will then pull this all together in a file and check this into the GitHub pages repo, which is where we host our blog.This will be a Live Coding session, so join us on Wed at 8:30 and see if we can pull this off or watch it go back into the backlog. Either way, this will be fun to see.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Static Site Generation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/07/28/Static-Site-Generators.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Static Site Generation" /><published>2021-07-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-07-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/video/2021/07/28/Static-Site-Generators</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/video/2021/07/28/Static-Site-Generators.html">&lt;p&gt;Static Site Generators are a great way to build a website that is based more on content.  While you could build any type of site, it’s perfect for blogs, documentation, books, and content-heavy sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this show we talked about using a static site generator to build a content site without the hassle of writing and maintaining several pages of html and css layout.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also easily host a site that uses Jekyll on GitHub Pages because support is built right in.  IT doesn’t mean you can’t host any static site with GitHub Pages.  You can use your favorite tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/c_T_jNYDAQo&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Rich Ross</name></author><category term="video" /><summary type="html">Static Site Generators are a great way to build a website that is based more on content. While you could build any type of site, it’s perfect for blogs, documentation, books, and content-heavy sites.In this show we talked about using a static site generator to build a content site without the hassle of writing and maintaining several pages of html and css layout.You can also easily host a site that uses Jekyll on GitHub Pages because support is built right in. IT doesn’t mean you can’t host any static site with GitHub Pages. You can use your favorite tools.</summary></entry></feed>